

New York City Metro Area • aditya@pandya.co • LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Product Leader with 15+ years of experience in orchestrating systemic changes and scaling multi-sided B2C ecosystems 10X. Generated \$6B+ in revenue, and built high-performing teams of up to 12 product managers and leaders across global markets. Combines strategic leadership and a strong understanding of AI to deliver intuitive experiences that solve hard problems at scale.

EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT ADVISOR at VARIOUS STARTUPS

May 2023 - Present

Advised early/growth-stage startups (Marketplaces, HR Tech, Automotive) on product strategy

- Delivered data-driven insights to C-suite executives, shaping critical decisions with multi-million dollar impact
- Guided teams through pivotal growth phases, driving substantial revenue and retention improvements

INDEED
SENIOR DIRECTOR OF PRODUCT

February 2016 - May 2023

July 2022 - May 2023

Led a team of 12 product managers & leaders, building products used by 100M+ job seekers and 5M+ businesses

- Built and launched Al-powered profiles, improving visibility for 350M+ job seekers, driving \$400M ARR
- Pioneered Al-first experiences, delivering personalized job recommendations for 50M+ monthly job seekers
- Developed an intelligent content engine, improving job recommendation relevance for 35M+ job seekers
- Scaled matching products (Resume Search, Instant Match), expanding the qualified candidate pool by 60M

DIRECTOR OF PRODUCT

October 2019 - June 2022

Directed 8 product managers focused on the Applications pillar used by 45M+ job seekers and 2M+ businesses

- Reimagined job application experience, making Indeed #1 globally and adding \$1B+ revenue with 1M+ hires
- Built APIs for AI-powered chatbots on WhatsApp, Messenger & web, enabling conversational job applications
- Launched Interview Scheduling from 0 to 10M+ annual interviews, reducing time-to-hire from weeks to 6 days

SENIOR MANAGER OF PRODUCT

January 2018 - September 2019

Led a team of 5 product managers to scale Indeed's flagship job application platform, Indeed Apply

- Scaled Indeed Apply from 300M to 1B+ annual applications, directly impacting multi-billion dollar revenue
- Launched ML-powered application experience; removed 13M low-quality applications/month with \$380M ARR
- Established Indeed Apply as primary application method on 1000+ sites and marketplaces, including Glassdoor

PRODUCT MANAGER

February 2016 - December 2017

Managed a team of 2 product managers for Indeed's flagship job application platform, Indeed Apply

- Optimized job application experience, lifting conversions 12% and adding 9-figure ARR
- Launched developer program for "Indeed Apply", driving 9-figure revenue growth from employers and partners
- Built Apply Everywhere to help 7M+ monthly job seekers apply on third-party sites using their Indeed Profile

PRODUCT MANAGER at MAKEMYTRIP

April 2014 - January 2016

Led growth initiatives for mobile app and Hotels vertical of India's #1 Online Travel Platform

- Drove mobile app and Hotels initiatives, generating 8-figure revenue and 91% year-over-year shopper growth
- Spearheaded launch of new mobile apps, achieving 4.6+ rating and featured status in App/Google Play Stores

PRODUCT & UX MANAGER at DIRECTI

May 2010 - February 2014

Led 4 product managers and designers for Flock (enterprise messaging) and BigRock (hosting/domain provider)

- Scaled Flock to 1.5M monthly active users in 18 months via product-led growth and user-centric design
- Executed global expansion and referral program, driving 6-figure ARR and 36% revenue growth in 6 months

FOUNDER at TOTALBARÇA

September 2009 - 2019

Founded globally recognized community for FC Barcelona, attracting 1.2M+ monthly visitors and 780,000+ fans

- Embodied FC Barcelona's "More Than A Club" philanthropic ethos, donating \$32,000+ in revenue to UNICEF
- Fostered collaborations with FC Barcelona, earning recognition from Board, players, and major media outlets

SKILLS

PRODUCT STRATEGY & INNOVATION: Product Vision & Roadmap Development, Al-First Product Development, Evidence-Driven Decision Making, Marketplace Optimization, Business Model Innovation

LEADERSHIP & TALENT DEVELOPMENT: Cross-Functional Team Leadership, Managing Product Leaders, Hiring & Team Building, Distributed Team Management (6+ Countries), Mentoring & Career Development

GROWTH & EXECUTION: Revenue Generation (\$6B+), Scaling Products (10x+), A/B Testing & Experimentation, User Research & Insights, International Product Scaling

ORGANIZATIONAL LEADERSHIP: Strategic Partnerships & Integration, Complex Stakeholder Management, Organizational Change Navigation, Executive Communication, Strategic Resource Allocation

EDUCATION

NARSEE MONJEE INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT STUDIES

Master of Business Administration (MBA), Marketing Bachelor of Technology (BTech), Information Technology